(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
う〜ん
Uun...
待っとれよ
Wait up!
あー
Ah!
にこにこ？
Smiling?
あらあら
My, my.
は〜む
Yawn...
えい！
Take that!
眠たい？
Are you sleepy?
チョコも眠たい
Choco is sleepy too.
ちょ〜こ
Cho~co.
待って待って待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
あ？
Huh?
にゃー
Meow!
あ、う〜ん
Ah, uun.
どっち？
Which one?
やだやだやだやだ！
No, no, no, no!
どーもー！ホロライブ2期生、悪魔の保健医、癒月ちょこでーす！
Hello! Hololive 2nd Generation, demonic school nurse, Yuzuki Choco here!
おめ、何しよーちゃ？
You, what are you doing?
うわ〜！
Whoa!
Thank you so much, thank you very much
ほら、豚、登って。頑張って、豚
Come on, pig, climb! Keep going, pig!
ほら、豚、こっちよ、こっち。どっち？
Come on, pig, over here, over here. Which one?
はい、はい、はい、はい！
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
なんだろう？
What is it?
何年やってると思ってるんですか？ え？
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Eh?
先生に向かってなんですか、その言葉遣いは
What is that attitude/language to your teacher?
友達じゃないんですよ。いいですか？
We are not friends. You got that?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
I am Yuzuki Choco-sensei, you know!
あ、やばい！うわー！
Ah, oh no! Waaah!
美味しかったの？
Was it delicious?
あ、違う！だめ！
Ah, no! Stop!
あー！
Aaa!
チョコしかおらん
There's only Choco.
また落ちた！
I fell again!
はい、いらっしゃいませ〜
Yes, welcome~
どこ？2期生？
Where? 2nd Gen?
2期生、2期生
2nd Gen, 2nd Gen.
あー！
Aaah!
おやすみ〜
Good night~
あ〜あ
Sigh...
うっし
Alright!
はぁ〜、保健室。
Haa... the nurse's office.
保健室のベッドでお昼寝した〜い。
I want to take a nap in the school nurse's office bed.
ずる休み
Playing hooky...
スルーされない
I won't be ignored.
保健室は神聖なの
The nurse's office is sacred.
サボってる？
Are you slacking off?
今日だけよ
Only for today.
誰も来ない やる気出ない
No one's coming, I have no motivation.
ちょこちょこ センセーション
Choco-Choco Sensation!
このままじゃ私だめみたい
At this rate, I look like I'm no good.
はぁ 起きなきゃ
Haa, I have to wake up...
布団だから
but because of my futon...
2回目のあくび おやすみなさい
My second yawn, good night.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry,
少しだけ寝かせて 先生モード
let me sleep just a bit, Teacher Mode...
ゆらぐ心をめぐる感情くすぐる
Emotions circling my wavering heart are tickling me.
一度じゃ甘いの？せーしょん
Is once not sweet enough? Sensation.
癒やされたい 甘えていたいとゆう
Want to be healed, want to be spoiled, a...
ちょこせんせーしょん
...Choco-sensation.
君の視線 君の体温
Your perspective, your body temperature...
わかってても恋は測れない
...even if I know them, love cannot be measured.
元気なのにため息しちゃう
Even though I'm energetic, I find myself sighing.
もしかしてもう手遅れ？
Could it be that it's already too late?
でも どっちどっちするまで動けないから
But I can't move until I decide one way or the other...
ドキドキ運んできてね 毎終電
...so please bring the excitement, on every last train.
ちょこちょこ せーしょん (いぇい！)
Choco-choco-sensation (Yay!)
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you too.
はーい！ということで！
Hi! And so!
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026、始まりました！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 has begun!
見て見て！一曲目から、ちょこ、生まれ変わりました！
Look, look! From the very first song, Choco has been reborn!
いや、今日はね、原点回帰ということで...
Well, today, as a return to my roots...
ちょこのなんと、保健室ステージなの！
...it's actually Choco's school nurse's office stage!
いや、ちょっと保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって...
Yes, the school nurse's office has also been reborn...
めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりました！
...and has become super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとかできそうだよね！
It looks like we could do situation dramas here!
今日は生まれ変わったニューちょこと、
Today, along with the reborn New Choco...
素敵なゲスト様をいっぱい呼んで、ライブをしていくんだけど...
...I've invited lots of wonderful guests to do a live show, but...
その前にみんな、ちょこのこと、もっと見たいよね？
...before that, everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも、まだダメだよ？
Ah, but not just yet, okay?
これから来るお二人に、ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいました！
I've requested a photoshoot of Choco from the two who are coming!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう！
So without further ado, let's call them out!
ノエル様！ラミィ様！
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
あーー！わーー！
Ahhh! Woahhh!
来たよー！
We're here!
せーの、ちょこ先生、
One, two... Choco-sensei!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
えー、ということで今回はね、この可愛い両手に花で...
So, this time, with flowers in both of my hands...
可愛いお二人に、ちょっとね、ちょこの撮影会をしてってもらおうと思うんですけど...
...I'd like these two cuties to do a photoshoot of Choco...
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします！ノエルから！
...but first, please introduce yourselves! Noel, go ahead!
はい！えー、こんまっする！ホロライブ三期生の白銀ノエルと、
Yes! Kon-muscle! I'm Shirogane Noel, Hololive's 3rd gen...
はい！ホロライブ五期生の、顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
And I'm Yukihana Lamy, Hololive's 5th gen, whose face is a liver!
今日はよろしくお願いします！
We look forward to working with you today!
まあね、ちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところを...
Well, since Choco-sensei has gotten so cute...
ちょっと団長頑張って、攻めていこうと思いますので、よろしくお願いします！
...the Commander is going to do her best to be aggressive, so please look forward to it!
攻めて、攻めて、攻めて！
Attack, attack, attack!
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy is also going to push the limits!
いや、撮影会やるなら、このお二人を呼ぶしかないかなって思って、呼んじゃいました！
Well, if I was going to do a photoshoot, I thought I had to invite these two!
嬉しい！
We're so happy!
いや、しかも、しかも、ちょっと、あとね、この三人から、なんと、お知らせもあるみたいなので、
And moreover, the three of us also have an announcement to make!
お知らせ！？気になる！気になる！
An announcement?! I'm curious! I'm curious!
撮影会のあとで、皆様、楽しみにしててください！
Please look forward to it after the photoshoot!
楽しみだー！
We can't wait!
それじゃあ、ちょっと、こちらで撮影会、よろしくお願いします！
Well then, please take charge of the photoshoot here!
はーい！行こう、行こう！
Okay! Let's go, let's go!
えっほ、えっほ、えっほ、えっほ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
お！なんかすごいとこ来たぞ！
Oh! We've come to an amazing place!
え、すごい！可愛い！
Wow, amazing! So cute!
可愛いでしょ！可愛いでしょ！
Cute, right? Super cute, right?
撮影会は、ちょこのここの、診察室でやります！
The photoshoot will take place here in Choco's examination room!
おー！診察室だ！ちょこ先生の診察室！すげえ、可愛い！可愛い！
Oh! The examination room! Choco-sensei's examination room! It's so cute!
いいでしょ いいでしょ！
Great, isn't it? Great, isn't it?!
でも 診察室だけど ベッドは？ベッドどこ？
But even though it's a clinic... where's the b-bed? Where's the bed?
あ、なんかパネルのある…
Ah, there's a panel over there...
なんかパネルあれなくない？あれ使う？
Isn't there a panel over there? Shall we use that?
あ、ちょっとそこ、ダメ！
Ah, wait, not that one! No!
え、これダメなの？
Eh, is this no good?
そこは、後との面会で使うの！
We use that for the meetings later!
えー！何！？面会用！面会用！
Eh?! What?! For the meetings! For the meetings!
面会用？
For meetings?
そう、ちょっとね、ベッドとか、ちょっと色々、撮影会とか、シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって
Yes, so, with the bed and all, I thought we could do various things like photo shoots, or situational dramas...
シチュエーションドラマ？！
Situational drama?!
とんでもないことしようとしてる！
She's trying to do something outrageous!
本当だよ！
Seriously!
いやそうなんですよ。まあ、でもそれは置いておいて
Well, that's how it is. But putting that aside...
あ、置いておくんだ。
Ah, you're putting it aside.
ちょっと今回は、二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので
This time, I'd like the two of you to do the shooting.
まずは…
First...
ラミ様には、カメラを！
Lamy-sama gets the camera!
え、本格的な！すごい、カメラ来た！
Whoa, a professional one! Amazing, a camera's here!
そしてノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, this one, ta-da!
なんだいこれ？
What is this?
ちょこのギリギリを守るために、特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
To protect Choco's limits, it's a specially made mosaic bar!
特別！モザイク棒来た！
Special! A mosaic bar is here!
ボタンで、このモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい！
Apparently you can change the pixelation of this mosaic with a button!
今めっちゃ粗くなってるから。 / あ、本当、薄くできる！
Because right now it's super pixelated. / Ah, really, we can make it lighter!
本当だ！
Really!
すげえ。でも粗い方がむしろいいまであるな、これ。
Amazing. But the pixelated one might actually be better, honestly.
確かに。
Indeed.
隠すよ、これ大丈夫かな？でも配信ね、ちょっと守りますよ。
I'll hide it. Is this okay? But we'll protect the stream.
ちょこの配信を守ってください！
Please protect Choco's stream!
頑張ります！
We'll do our best!
それでは撮影会、スタート！
Well then, let the photo shoot begin!
イェーイ！まずはやっぱり全身？そうだね。
Yay! First, a full-body shot, of course? Yeah.
普通にね、ちょっとポーズ。いつものちょこ先生の…
Just a normal pose. The usual Choco-sensei...
こんな感じ？
Like this?
ああ！美しい！
Ah! Beautiful!
美しい！あ、いい、いい。
Beautiful! Ah, nice, nice.
え、可愛い！
Eh, cute!
もうここ、ちょっと不味いんじゃない？不味いかな…
Wait, isn't this already getting a bit dangerous? Is it bad?
逆に？逆に？
In reverse? In reverse?
ノリノリなんですけど！
You are totally into it!
不味いかな？ちょっと、ちょっとね。ここ揺れてる。
Is it bad? Just a little, just a little. It's shaking here.
モザイク、モザイクが追いついてない！
The mosaic, the mosaic can't keep up!
追いついてない！
It's not keeping up!
ノエル様頑張って！
Noel-sama, do your best!
こうやってね。あ、こういう感じで。
Like this. Ah, like this, right?
ちょっとジャンプしてもらい、見てもらっても、ジャンプ確かに。
Can you try jumping? Let's see. Jumping, indeed.
えい！
Ei!
あ、揺れる！めっちゃ揺れる！あかん、これあかんでしょ、これ！
Ah, it's shaking! It's shaking so much! No, this is bad, right?!
あい、あい、おい！
Ai, ai, oi!
あら。
Oh my.
せっかくだから椅子とかも座っちゃう？
Since we're here, should we sit on the chair?
椅子ね、ここに。はーい。
The chair, over here. Okaay.
おお、いいですね。靴も可愛い！なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。
Oh, nice. The shoes are cute too! They're kind of blueish.
そう、ちょこね、そこが赤なの。
Yes, Choco's, the bottom is red.
ええ！！あ、不味い！
Eh?! Ah, dangerous!
ありがとうございます！そこがね、赤なの。これ。
Thank you very much! Yeah, that part's red. This.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
大丈夫、でも何か見えてないからね。大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, nothing is visible. Safe, safe.
守ってます、チャンネル守ってます！
We're protecting it, protecting the channel!
じゃあ今度は、上を、上を見てもらって。あ、いいね。
Now, can we look up? Ah, nice.
あら、可愛い！
Oh, cute!
見えてる？見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
Can you see? We can see, we can see!
見えてる？可愛い！いい、いい。
Can you see? Cute! Nice, nice.
あ、ちなみにラミさん。
Ah, by the way, Lamy-san...
あれですよ、この椅子に座って先生ポーズも希望しますけど。
That's it, we also requested a teacher pose while sitting on the chair.
そう！先生ポーズとってほしい！
Yes! I want you to strike a teacher pose!
先生ポーズって何だ？こんな感じ？
What is a teacher pose? Like this?
ああ、いい！いいですね、いい！非常に。
Ah, nice! It is very good, very! Extremely.
モザイクいらないね、これには。非常に。
We don't need the mosaic for this. Extremely.
非常にいらない？いや、わからない。ちょこ先生の魅力が溢れすぎてて。
Extremely unnecessary? Well, I don't know. Choco-sensei's charm is overflowing too much.
いいですね、素晴らしい。
Nice, wonderful.
じゃあ団長もいいですか？何なに？お尻ふりふりをちょっと、していただきたいんで。
Is the commander good with it too? What, what? I'd like to have her shake her hips a bit.
ふりふり、そう、後ろ向いてもらって。
Shake-shake, yeah, turn your back to us.
白衣越しだけど、ふりふり。あ、いいね！
Even through the lab coat, shake-shake. Ah, nice!
白衣越しだが、あの隙に…
It's through the lab coat, but in that gap...
あ、ちょっと、スカート結構際どい。
Ah, wait, the skirt is pretty close to the edge.
これ、白衣って、脱げ、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
Wait, the lab coat, can't you take it off? I want you to take it off.
脱げるけど、面会で、って言ってた。
I can take it off, but they said for the meetings.
あ、面会なら脱いでくれるんですね！
Ah, so you'll take it off for the meetings!
じゃあ逆にまた、ココ会長リスペクトということで、ガニ股、ガニ股好きなので。
In that case, showing respect to Coco-kaichou, I love the bowlegged stance, so a bowlegged one.
ガニ股？ガニ股！
Bowlegged? Bowlegged!
いいね！ガニ股助かる！ガニ股！
Nice! Bowlegged is a lifesaver! Bowlegged!
これちょっとモザイク、モザイク！
Wait, a bit of mosaic, mosaic!
ちょっと見えてるもんな、モザイクお願いします。
We can see it a bit, so mosaic please!
モザイクがむしろここが…逆にやばい！やばいやばいやばい！
The mosaic is rather... On the contrary, it's bad! Bad, bad, bad!
可愛い。ふぅ。
Cute. Whew.
どんどん行こう、どんどん行こう。
Let's keep going, let's keep going.
じゃあ、ラストは、やっぱアイドルだからさ、ちょこ先生。アイドル、とびきり可愛いアイドル、お願いします！
Well, for the last one, you are an idol after all, Choco-sensei. An idol, the ultimate cute idol, please!
はい！え、可愛い！
Yes! Eh, cute!
はい！
Yes!
いや、これ…あ、いいね。
Wow, this is... ah, nice.
うふふ。
(Giggles)
可愛い！
So cute!
いや、アップいい。顔のアップいい。可愛い。
Ah, close-ups are great. Close-ups of your face are nice. So cute!
たまりません。
It's irresistible.
可愛い、うーん。
Cute, mmm.
オッケー。いっぱいいただいた！ありがとう！
Okay! I got so many! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやちょっとね、この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので。
Well, we'll be doing the rest of this in members-only, so...
メン限ではちょっと、歌も撮影会もシチュエーションドラマも、何と二本やっちゃいます！
In members-only, we'll do songs, a photo shoot, and even two situation dramas!
やったー！楽しみ！
Yay! I'm looking forward to it!
ちなみにさ、何かタイトルとかあるの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, are there titles for those situation dramas?
あ、今回のタイトルが、
Ah, the titles this time are...
「先生と、ベッドで、特別バレンタイン」
"A Special Valentine in Bed with Teacher"
特別！？
Special!?
たまらん、たまらん！先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン！？
Irresistible, irresistible! A special Valentine in bed with teacher!?
ってタイトルと、
...is one title, and the other is...
「診察室で甘い処方箋を」っていう。
"A Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room."
甘い！甘い甘い甘い！
Sweet! Sweet, sweet, sweet!
最高すぎる。
That's too awesome.
あの、目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて、
And for the POV, we'll have the cameraman lie on the bed,
ちょっとみんなが本当に見えるように、Chocoが覆いかぶさるように、
so you can really see Choco leaning over you...
いろんな画角で撮っていきたいと思います。
I'd like to take shots from various angles.
楽しみ、楽しみ！
I can't wait!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ということで、そろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、
So, we're running out of time,
ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います！
so we should head back to the live show!
こんな気持ちで！？あ、ライブだった！そうだ！
In this mood!? Ah, right, we're doing a live show! Yes!
急げー！
Hurry, hurry!
うわー！やったー！
Whoa! Yay!
はーい！
Yes!
というわけで、この後、二人それぞれちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど、
So, next, each of them will do a duet with me,
最後に三人でも歌うので、楽しみにしといてください！
and at the very end, we'll sing as a trio, so look forward to it!
楽しみ！お楽しみに！
I'm excited! Please look forward to it!
それではお着替えに行きましょうか。
Shall we go change our outfits now?
お、これ？すごい！可愛い。
Oh, this one? Amazing! So cute.
リボンもついてる。可愛い。
It even has a ribbon. Cute.
じゃ、ちょっとカーテンの裏で、
Well, behind the curtain,
お着替え行ってきます！
we're going to change!
行ってきます！
See you soon!
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
そろそろ とろりベイビーベイビー
It's about time, melting baby baby
とろけちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Melt away and catch me, darling
ピュアピュア 心はフワリ
Pure, pure, my heart is light and fluffy
ユルユル ワンツー
Loose, loose, one, two
なんか眠れない夜には
On a night I can't sleep for some reason
お散歩
I'll go for a walk
特別なパーティータイム
A special party time
二人きり
Just the two of us
あの角曲がれば
If we turn that corner
ペンギンしかいない公園だよ
It's a park with only penguins
蒸し暑い空気の中
Through the humid air
迷い込むんだ
We'll wander in
コンビニにちょっと寄り道
Taking a little detour to the convenience store
甘いアイスじゃなくて
Not sweet ice cream
これがいい
I want this
あのお酒 ほろよい
That drink, "Horoyoi"
ウィンクで ストロング
A "Strong" with a wink
リキュールじゃもう
With just liqueur
酔えない
I can't get drunk
ラムで潰して お願い
Knock me out with rum, please
お砂糖はなしなしで
No sugar at all
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして
Melt it in the scorching heat
ゴクゴク飲んで
Drink it right down
クセのある私のことを
With all my quirks,
大事にしてよね
take good care of me, okay?
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
そろそろ とろりベイビーベイビー
It's about time, melting baby baby
とろけちゃってキャッチミーダーリン
Melt away and catch me, darling
ピュアピュア 心はフワリ
Pure, pure, my heart is light and fluffy
ユルユル ワンツー
Loose, loose, one, two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely way home
フラフラ
Dizzy and staggering
特別なボーナスタイム
A special bonus time
手をつなごう
Let's hold hands
おっきめ Tシャツ
An oversized T-shirt
君に借りた ありがとうって
I borrowed from you, saying thank you
ヒロインにして
Make me your heroine
困らせたいんだ
I want to tease you
コンビニまた寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しいな
It's so fun
もう一本だけ
Just one more can,
弱いヤツ
a weak one
トロトロに 酔える気？
Feeling a bit tipsy?
テンパリングが大事
Tempering is important...
熱すぎても 飽きちゃって
...even if it's too hot, we'll get tired of it...
冷たいのはダメ、やだもん
...and cold is no good, I hate it!
チョコみたいな私を
Like chocolate, me...
プレシャスにして 扱って
...treat me as someone precious.
炭酸のお酒で
With sparkling alcohol...
シュワシュワシュワ
...fizzy, fizzy, fizzy!
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless you express it...
恋してる証拠に ここでチューして
...as proof of your love, kiss me right here!
夜空のグラスに
In the glass of the night sky...
キラキラをオンして
...adding toppings of sparkles...
息もできないくらいに 踊って自爆して
...dance so much that we can't even breathe!
だって だって だって
Because, because, because...
恋に溺れて
...I'm drowning in love!
君の熱で溶けたら
If I melt from your warmth...
そのまま食べてよ
...eat me just like that!
手、ベトベトついたって Limits
Even if your hands get all sticky...
いっしょ、いっしょ
...we're together, together!
甘いお酒 ほろ酔い
Tipsy on sweet alcohol...
ウインクでストロング
...a wink makes it strong.
リキュールじゃもう 酔えない
Liqueur can't make me drunk anymore...
ラブで満たして お願い
...please fill me with love!
お砂糖は増しましで
With extra, extra sugar...
甘い甘さじゃ足りない_
...just sweet sweetness is not enough.
灼熱で溶かして
Melt it with burning heat...
特急で飲んで_
...and drink it express!
癖のある私だからさ_
Because I have my quirks, you see..._
君に選ばれたサマーチョコレート_
...I'm the summer chocolate chosen by you!
トロトロトロンにベイビー
Melty-melty, baby!
とろけちゃってハッピー_
Melted and happy!
ぴゅあぴゅあ ココアふわり
Pure pure cocoa softly..._
うるうる ワン・ツー_
...teardrop eyes, one, two!
いぇーい！
Yay!
What's up, everybody?
Can you hear me?
It's Yozora Mel!_
Noel-chan, dōzo!_
Noel-chan, go ahead!
To my sweet badas? Yes, Shirogane Noel is in the house!
It's time to get up!_
We have a hot new song!
That's from AKB48!
To make you feel good!_
Koisuru Fortune Cookie!_
So let's jump and crazy!
あなたのことが好きなのに
Even though I love you...
私にまるで興味ない
...you have absolutely no interest in me.
何度目かの失恋の準備
Preparing for my umpteenth heartbreak...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の_
If I look around, there are so many...
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん_
...cute girls everywhere._
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You won't notice a plain flower like me.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れるMusic_
Music is playing in the cafeteria..._
ぼんやり聴いていたら_
...as I listen to it blankly.
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ_
Before I know it, to the rhythm..._
つま先から動き出す
...my toes start to move.
止められない今の気持ち_
I can't stop these feelings now.
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー_
Come on, come on, come on, come on baby..._
占ってよ
...tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー!_
Koisuru Fortune Cookie!_
未来は そんな悪くないよ_
The future isn't that bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
To bring good luck, show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Heart-shaped fortune cookie...
運勢 今日よりもよくしよう_
...let's make our luck better than today!_
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!_
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね_
Life isn't so bad after all, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる_
A wonderful miracle will happen..._
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
...a feeling that we'll love each other somewhere.
あなたのことが好きなのに
Even though I like you,
私にまるで興味ない
you have absolutely no interest in me.
何度目かの失恋の準備
Preparing myself for yet another heartbreak...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いいコがいいなんて
They say they prefer girls with good personalities,
男の子は言うけれど
or so boys like to say,
ルックスがアドバンテージ
but looks are an advantage.
いつだって可愛いコが
Since the cute girl always...
人気投票1位になる保存
...comes first in the popularity vote.
Please Please Please Oh Baby
私も見て
Look at me too!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Love Fortune Cookie!
その殻さあ壊してみよう保存
Come on, break that shell open.
Hey Hey Hey
先の展開
What lies ahead...
神様も知らない保存
...even God doesn't know.
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
Tearful Fortune Cookie...
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative!
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is overflowing with love.
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
Making you forget all the sad things.
明日は明日の風が吹くと
Believing that tomorrow is another day...
思う
...and things will work out.
Come on Come on Come on Come on Baby
占ってよ
Predict my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Love Fortune Cookie!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't so bad.
Hey Hey Hey
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To summon luck, you have to show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Heart Fortune Cookie,
運勢今日よりもよくしよう保存
let's make our fortune better than today's.
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't something to throw away, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
An astonishing miracle will happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
A premonition that we'll love each other somewhere.
君が好きったら君が好き！
If I say I like you, I like you!
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love...
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ保存
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love!
あのね乙女は本気出すと凄いんです
You know, girls are incredible when they get serious.
One, Two, いずれシチュ
One, Two, eventually...
あの手この手でライバルを出し抜くの
Outsmarting rivals with one trick or another,
全部計算済み レシピ通り
all calculated according to the recipe!
好きだって武器にして
Using my love as a weapon,
手繋いでみたりして保存
even trying to hold hands...
うっとり甘えて
...gazing rapturously and playing coy...
既にGet Ready!
...we are already get ready!
あ、手元が...
Ah, my hand...
つまみ食いしたら無くなった？
Did it disappear because you snuck a bite?
お砂糖、いや日本酒
Sugar? No, Japanese sake!
急にファンキー
Suddenly funky!
苦いのはNGで
Bitter is a definite no-go.
女の子の季節だもん全部
Since it's a girl's season, everything...
思い通りになってよね
...must go exactly as planned, you know?
君は私と結ばれます
You are bound to be with me.
本命あげちゃうメルティ
I'll give you my true feelings, Melty.
誰にも渡さない大戦争
The great war where I won't hand you over to anyone!
ときめいちゃいますメルティ
My heart is fluttering, Melty!
それじゃ手と手繋いじゃう？
Shall we hold hands then?
内緒のデート
A secret date,
Sweet Sweet Key
甘くていいの？
Is it sweet enough?
Sweet Sweet Heart
こういうのがいいでしょ？
This is how it should be, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's first love,
絶対譲らない覚悟です
I'm determined to never hand you over.
本気なのです
I'm dead serious.
目を見て言って
Look me in the eyes and say it:
君の気持ち
Your feelings!
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love...
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ保存
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love!
Girls Battle Field!
あの子と喋ってんの？
Are you talking to that girl?
Girls Battle Field!
意思表示がちょっと...
Your expression of intent is a little...
Girls Battle Field!
大丈夫、へこたれないもん
It's okay, I won't lose heart!
惚れさせたら勝ちです
Once I make you fall for me, I win!
ハチミツをドバッと入れちゃうな
I'll pour in a ton of honey!
砂糖の量は愛の量
The amount of sugar is the amount of love.
間違えたこれ塩だった
Wait, I made a mistake, this was salt.
マーブルマフィン
Marble muffin,
焦る気持ちをトッピングして
topping it with my impatient feelings...
真心込めてラッピング
...and wrapping it with all my heart!
自分も本気コーデでいく
I'm going with my serious outfit too.
祈るラブチャンス！
Praying for a love chance!
なんども試作した
Often I've rehearsed this,
予行練習もした
I've done dress rehearsals, too.
夜明けになどなるな
Don't let dawn come just yet.
大丈夫自分史上1番可愛い私なんだから
It's okay, because I'm the cutest version of myself in history!
君は私と結ばれます
You will be bound to me,
結ばれる運命なのです
it is our destiny to be bound together.
本命あげちゃう めるきゅん
I'll give you my heart, Mel-kyun!
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
This is a great war I won't let anyone win!
ときめいちゃいます
My heart is throbbing!
めるしーそれじゃ手と手つなげないじゃん
Merci, at this rate, we can't even hold hands, can we?
内緒のデート
Our secret date...
ツイツイ キス
Oops, a kiss!
甘くていいの
Is sweet okay?
ツイツイ ハグ
Oops, a hug!
こういうのがいいっしょ
This kind of thing is the best, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's my first love!
絶対譲らない覚悟です 大きな愛です
I'm determined never to give in, it's a big love!
目を見て言って
Look into my eyes and say it,
君の気持ち
your feelings.
ピュアラ ピュアラ
Pure-ah, Pure-ah...
ピュアラ ピュアラブ
Pure-ah, Pure-ah, Love!
はーい！ということで
All right! So,
ちょこたち3人の新曲でしたー！
that was our new song by the three of us!
改めまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にね
Once again, in collaboration with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama,
コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど
we sang this new song, "Hatsukoi Daisensou"...
今回作詞作曲をMEDANSY様
And this time, the lyrics and composition are by MEDANSY-sama,
そして編曲をYousuke様にお願いいたしました！
and the arrangement is by Yousuke-sama!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今回のテーマがバレンタインの日に
The theme this time is about Valentine's Day,
3人の可愛い女の子たちが1人の男の子を手に入れるために
where three cute girls, trying to win over one boy,
バチバチに出し抜こうとするみたいな
passionately try to outdo each other...
激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております！
It is a super sweet themed song!
いいね、可愛い！可愛い！
Nice! So cute! Cute!
そう！3人の声が合わさってめちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので
Yes! Our three voices blended to make it a total idol song,
ぜひぜひ皆様、聴いてください！
so please, everyone, listen to it!
えー、何回も聴きたいなー。
I want to listen to it over and over.
ねー何回も聴きたい！聴けるところあるのかな？
Right, over and over! Is there a place where we can listen to it?
こちらの楽曲、このあと24時から
Actually, this song, starting from midnight tonight,
2月の15日0時からね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
which is February 15th at 0:00 AM, will be released on various music sites!
やったー！聴ける！
Yay! We can listen to it!
そしてね、この配信後、すぐに
And, right after this release, immediately...
この楽曲のMVが！
this song's music video...
公開されます！やったー！
will be released! Yay!
ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聴いて、MVの方にも感想とかね
Please, everyone, listen to it a lot, and leave some thoughts...
コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなって思います！
and comments on the MV as well! We'd be so happy!
お願いします！
Please do!
じゃあね、2人とも今日はありがとう！
Well then, thank you both for today!
お誕生日おめでとう！ありがとう、嬉しい！
Happy birthday! Thank you, I'm so happy!
引き続き頑張ってね！
Keep doing your best!
頑張るー！ありがとう！
I'll do my best! Thank you!
それじゃあ、ちょっと、おさらばじゃ！
Well then, I'll be off!
おさらば！ありがとう！
Bye-bye! Thank you!
そして、ここからライブ後半となります！
And from here, we enter the second half of the live show!
まだまだゲストパートとか、なんと最後に
We still have guest segments, and even at the very end,
重大告知もあるので、皆様、一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
a major announcement! Let's all have fun together!
それでは、次のゲストはこちら！
Now, here is the next guest!
大人なフリして。
[Song: Pretending to Be an Adult]
急に会いたいって
Suddenly saying you want to meet,
いつものように準備してる
I prepare just as I always do.
午前零時過ぎの終電で向かうって返した
I replied that I'd head over on the last train past midnight.
やめときなよって言われても
Even if I'm told to stop...
また会いに行く 会いたいから
I'll go see you again, because I want to see you.
別々に落ち合う 街の風は少し冷たい
Meeting up separately, the city breeze is a little cold.
慣れないワイン 無理矢理飲み干してしまってはフラフラ
Gulping down wine I'm not used to, I'm already feeling dizzy.
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手にしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess things up?
少しも残したくない
I don't want to leave even a little bit behind.
ちょっと期待してね
Anticipating just a bit...
ずっと見栄張ってね
constantly putting on airs...
周りばかり気にして生きている
always living while worrying about others.
ちょっと憂鬱かも でもなんか寂しくてあぁ
Maybe I'm a bit depressed, but somehow I feel lonely, ah.
本当の自分じゃない気がして
Feeling like I'm not my true self.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself even though I'm not like that.
価値のないキスでも やっぱ一番嬉しくて
Even a worthless kiss makes me the happiest.
取り繕った私は可愛いかな？
I wonder if my made-up self is cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hug me tight enough to break.
今にも切れそうな糸で繋がっている恋だね
This is a love connected by a thread that's about to break.
私が諦めたらきっと簡単に消えちゃうね
If I give up, it'll surely disappear so easily.
引き留めるにはどうする？
What should I do to hold you back?
あの子だったらどうする？
What would that girl do?
不器用に唇を絡めて
Awkwardly intertwining our lips.
いつもチェックしてね
Always check on me,
息苦しい腕で
with your stifling arms.
他の子と比べてばかりいた
You were always comparing me to other girls.
一番見てほしい あなたの目の前の私は
The one I want you to look at the most is me right in front of you,
どこか違う景色見てる
yet you're looking at some other scenery.
いつも優しいフリして
Always pretending to be kind,
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
smiling even though you're not like that.
近づけば近づくほど心は遠くなって
The closer we get, the further apart our hearts become.
少しずつ離れていくことは分かるよ
I know we're slowly drifting apart.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hug me tight enough to forget everything.
自分はもっと強いと
If only I were stronger,
言えばさよならを言えるのにね
then I could say goodbye.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself even though I'm not like that.
ふと見せる優しさがずっと忘れられなくて
I can never forget the kindness you suddenly show.
取り繕った私は可愛いかな？
I wonder if my made-up self is cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hug me tight enough to break.
零れだした涙
The tears that began to overflow,...
私頑張ったよね
I really tried my best, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると思っていたもういいから
I thought you'd turn to look at me someday, but it's fine now.
取り繕った私は流れていく
My made-up self is washing away.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hug me tight enough to forget everything.
chocolate box
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always seem so sleepy,
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
and you always seem so bored.
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
You always seem so sketchy,
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
and you're always on your phone.
ホントはテンション高いのに
Though you're actually usually hyper,...
アタシといると超低いし
you're so quiet when you're with me.
なんなん自分?ありえなくない?
What is up with you? That's unbelievable!
嫌い、大嫌い。どうでもいい!!
I hate you, I really hate you! Whatever!!
だったらボクも言うけどさぁ!
Well, then I've got some things to say too!
ちっちゃい事で すぐ怒るし
You get mad easily over tiny things,
言い返したら すぐ泣くし
and when I talk back, you cry right away.
ごめんって言っても 許してくれないし
Even when I say sorry, you don't forgive me.
その割 一夜が明けちゃえば
But despite all of that, the next morning...
ケロっと おはようとか言うし
you'll nonchalantly say "Good morning!"
あぁ なんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are.
畜生!! もう知らないぞ!!
Dammit!! I'm done with you!!
甘い甘い恋 of 魔法箱 (甘い甘い恋の魔法箱)
A sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
a secret chocolate tasting of outer space.
二人だけのデコレーションを
Let's scatter our own decorations...
散りばめて彩って食べちゃおうか!
and decorate it before we eat it up!
デコレーションを 散りばめて色とりどって食べちゃおうか
Shall we scatter and decorate it, and eat it up!
苦い苦い愛の溜まり箱 未来味の不思議なチョコレート
Bitter, bitter, love's treasure box / Future-flavored mysterious chocolate
温めて混ぜたらきっと
Once warmed and mixed, it will surely...
いつかお口に合う味になるの
...someday become a taste that suits our mouths.
ねえねえちょっといいかな
Hey, hey, can I ask you something?
何？
Why?
さっきはあのね ごめんね
About earlier, you know, sorry...
何が？
What about it?
いつももやっとなるじゃん
We always get annoyed, don't we?
それで？
So?
今日はこれを渡したくて 言葉じゃ足りないからさ──
Today, I wanted to give you this... Because words aren't enough, you see.
だから！
That's why!
受け取ってくれないかな
Won't you accept it?
何を？
What is it?!
いっしょにいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me.
わぁぁぁ！
Whaaaaaaa...
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃう
I end up indulging in your kindness...
誰よりも近いから 素直になれない
...because we are closer than anyone else, I can't be honest.
君の一生懸命さに ついつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting your earnestness...
誰よりも一番 大好きなのに
...even though I love you more than anyone.
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
Sweet, sweet, dream's treasure box...
奇跡味の秘密のチョコレート
...miracle-flavored secret chocolate.
二人だけのイノベーションを 探し組み立てたら
Shall we search and build our own innovation, just for the two of us...
にぎやかそうか
...and make it lively!
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱保存
Bitter, bitter, daily vanity box...
世界味の最初のチョコレート
...world-flavored first chocolate.
冷め切って割れないように
Don't let it cool down and break,
大事に包んで生涯の完成まで
carefully wrap it until the completion of our lifetime.
いつだって
Anytime...
病めるときも
...even when sick.
どんな日も合わわわ
Any day...
そうずっと
...yes, forever.
健やかなるときも
Even when healthy,
手をとって 死が二人を分かつまで
take my hand, until death parts us two.
愛してる
I love you.
僕もそうさ
Me too.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
そばにいるよ
I'm by your side.
なんて嘘かもよ？
Is that a lie, perhaps?
あぁそうかい 僕も適当に言った
Ah, is that so? I said it randomly too.
甘い甘い？
Sweet, sweet?
苦い苦い
Bitter, bitter...
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
Sweet, sweet, love's magic box...
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
...universe-flavored secret chocolate.
二人だけのデコレーションを 散りばめて色とりどって食べちゃおうか
Shall we scatter and decorate it, just for the two of us, and eat it up!
苦い苦い愛の溜まり箱
Bitter, bitter, love's treasure box...
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
...future-flavored mysterious chocolate.
温めて混ぜたら完璧たい
Once warmed and mixed, it's perfect!
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
Someday it will become the happiest taste ever.
いっせーので Thank you so much! See you next time!
One, two, three! Thank you so much! See you next time!
告白日和、です！
[It's a Perfect Day for a Confession!]
ねえ ひとつだけ聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask you just one thing?
私のこと...
About me...
会えるかな 今日は
Maybe we can meet today,
心が騒いで
my heart is racing,
スキップしたくなった
I felt like skipping,
ときめきに躍る瞬間
the moment I dance with excitement.
私のことなど
About me...
たぶん気にしてないのだけど
You probably aren't even thinking about me, but...
ここにいるんだよ
I'm right here!
私はここだよ
自信が揺らぐ
My confidence is swaying,
嫌われてないかな
I wonder if you hate me?
いきおいで
With momentum,
とにかく挨拶だ！
I'll just say hello anyway!
やっと晴れたね パッと晴れたね
It's finally cleared up! It's cleared up suddenly!
そして元気になるね
And I feel energetic!
「おはよう」の代わりに 背中をたたいて
I'll pat your back instead of saying 'Good morning.'
さあ行くよ！
Alright, let's go!
やっと晴れたら パッと晴れたら_
Once it's finally cleared up, suddenly cleared up,
きっと元気な笑顔
surely, an energetic smile!
なんだか今のこの気持ちが せつなくなったよ
Somehow, these feelings I have right now have become painful!
授業はうわの空
My mind is on something else even during class,
遠くを眺めた
looking far away.
恋って甘いもんだよね
Isn't love sweet?
違うかもつらさ半分
Maybe it's different, half painful.
夢見るだけより
Rather than just dreaming,
触って確かめなきゃだから
I have to touch and confirm it, so...
動きだそうよ
let's get moving...
自分らしくね
Be like yourself, right?
楽しく生きるの
Living happily,
毎日がキセキ
every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより勇気だそう！
Instead of regretting not saying it, let's find the courage!
ずっと前から うんと前から 聞いてみたくて待ってた
Since a long time ago, from a long time ago, I've been waiting, wanting to ask...
私から最初に伝えてしまえ「大好きです！」
I'll be the first to tell you, "I love you!"
ずっと前だよ うんと前だよ 聞いたことに答えて
It's been a long time, from a long time ago. Will you answer what I asked?
どんなふうに感じてるの全部見せてよ！
How are you feeling? Show me everything!
楽しく生きるの
Living happily,
毎日がキセキ
every day is a miracle.
本当は不安でも勇気だそう！
Even if I'm scared, let's find the courage!
だそう？
Find the courage?
うん！
Yeah!
ずっと前から うんと前から 聞いてみたくて待ってた
Since a long time ago, from a long time ago, I've been waiting, wanting to ask...
私から最初に伝えてしまえ「大好きです！」
I'll be the first to tell you, "I love you!"
ずっと前だよ うんと前だよ 聞いたことに答えて
It's been a long time, from a long time ago. Will you answer what I asked?
どんなふうに感じてるの全部見せてよ！
How are you feeling? Show me everything!
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
My world is falling in love, arrows of light pierce my chest.
君をわかりたいんだよ 「ねえ、教えて」
I want to understand you. "Hey, tell me."
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔 涙こぼれて
Just a little regret over words that passed by, tears spilled over.
忙しい感情 鼓動にリンクする
Busy emotions link with my heartbeat.
チューニング
Tuning.
確かめたいんだ
I want to confirm this.
目的ばっかにとらわれて 大事なものが霞んで逃げて
Caught up only in my purpose, important things fade and run away...
今日もリスタート
Restart again today.
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
My world is falling in love, arrows of light pierce my chest.
全部わかりたいんだよ 「ねえ、聞かせて」
I want to understand everything. "Hey, let me hear it."
たった1ミリが遠くて
That one millimeter is too far.
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I ran through,
忘れない忘れられない
unforgettable, unforgettable,
輝く 1ページ
a shining page.
お似合いの二人になんだか複雑な気持ちがいるよ
Somehow it's a complicated feeling seeing the two of you look so good together.
初めての感情 鼓動にリンクする
My first emotion links with my heartbeat.
体温計...
I wonder if my thermometer...
…ちゃったかな？
...I wonder?
自分のことわからないまま
Though I still don't know myself very well,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even gave her advice,
胸が痛いや
and it made my chest hurt.
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
The whole world is falling in love, an arrow of light striking our chests.
気づいたこの想いは 「もう、遅いの」
I've just realized these feelings, "is it too late?"
あの子のほうが可愛いのに知ってるよだけど
I know that she's cuter than I am, but...
「うまくいかないで」なんてね 逃げ出したくせに
"I hope it doesn't work out," I thought, even though I'm the one who ran away.
ちょこ、君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃった。これが恋だって、初めて気づいたの。
Choco, I found myself wanting to know everything about you. I finally realized that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい。遅かったけど、諦めたくない。
I definitely want you to look my way. Even if it's late, I don't want to give up.
だって、好きだから！
Because, I love you!
春に咲いた
The flower that bloomed...
花が恋をした
...in spring fell in love.
花は
The flower...
必死に上を向いて笑った
...desperately looked upward and smiled.
青い夏の
A bud...
蕾も恋をした
...in the blue summer also fell in love.
咲かない花と
An unopened flower...
火薬の匂い
...and the scent of gunpowder.
本当の気持ち 言葉にして
I want to express my true feelings,
大事なこと 話せたら<
if I can say what is important...
今日もリスタート
...I'll restart today again.
鈍感な君だから
You're dense,
口に出していわなきゃ
so I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you now,
「ねえ、好きです」
"hey, I love you."
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
The whole world is falling in love, an arrow of light striking our chests.
全部わかりたいんだよ 「ねえ、聞かせて」
I want to understand everything, "hey, let me know."
たぐりよせて もうゼロセンチ
Pulling you close, to zero-centimeters...
駆け抜けた日々に
...in the days passing by.
忘れない 忘れない 輝く一ページ
I won't forget, I can't forget this one, shining page.
はい！ということで
Alright! And with that,
ここまではアキさま、ロボ子、
up until here, with Aki-sama, Roboco,
ござるに...
and Gozaru...
歌、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
we sang songs together!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
さてさて、ここからは
Well then, from here on,
なんと！重大告知が２つあります！
there are actually two major announcements!
まず１つ目が...
First, the first one is...
こちら！ドドン！
This! Ba-bam!
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2026！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to introduce it in a bit more detail.
まずは、こちら！
First, this one!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね、ちょこの誕生日といえば...
You know, speaking of Choco's birthday...
毎年、Nardack先生ありがとうございますということで！
Every year, I say thank you to Nardack-sensei!
今年もNardack先生に...
This year as well, Nardack-sensei...
めちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
drew this super lovely illustration for me!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで！
With this year's theme being Valentine's!
ちょっとね、チョコメイトを抱きながら...
Holding the Chocolat Mate...
ちょっと今回はチョコレート型のクッションにしてみました！
I made it into a chocolate-shaped cushion this time!
可愛いでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので
The size is just about like a pillow,
ちょっとねお昼寝のときとか、仮眠用に「すやぁ」ってできる
so you can use it for a quick nap, sleeping soundly with it,
感じで使えちゃいます！
like that!
そして、続いてはこちら！
And next is this one!
なんと！
Guess what!
今回
This time...
初めてちょっとね
...for the very first time,
お菓子が...
you can make sweets...
わー！
Wow!
しかもこちら！
What's more, here...
なんと、オリ曲に、ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが、
Incredibly, a story-linked voice drama...
一緒に、リリースされます！
...will be released together with the original songs!
いや、こちらね。
Well, you see,
約1話から12話まで！
from episode 1 to 12!
1曲ずつに連動して、
Linked to each individual song,
ボイスドラマもあるので、
there will also be a voice drama,
ぜひぜひ楽しみにしといてください！
so please look forward to them!
そして、今回はね。
And this time,
その記念すべき...
we will celebrate...
1曲目を、
the very first song...
これから披露したいと思います！
...by performing it right now!
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen to...
『キミの秒針』
"Your Second Hand."
まだ戻れないから
Because I can't go back yet,
また...
once more...
愛しさが増す
my affection grows.
キミに...
To you...
会いたいよ
I want to see you.
キミから受け取った
The fragile story
壊れそうなストーリー
I received from you...
どこまでも広がる
spread endlessly across...
青い青い空
...the blue, blue sky.
変わらない毎日も
The unchanging everyday life,
色のない夢も
and the colorless dreams...
手放して はじめようよ
Let's let go and begin.
不安の夜を数え
Counting the nights of anxiety,
泣きながら迎えた朝でもいい
even if we greet the morning in tears, it's fine.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち広がった
the engraved memories spread out.
戻れないから また
Because I can't go back, once more
愛しさが増す
my affection grows.
キミに会いたいよ
I want to see you.
二人で暖めた
The precious story
大切なストーリー...
we warmed together...
遠くまで続いた
The endless path
果てない道
that continued so far.
「疲れたら代わるから」
"I'll take over if you get tired,"
そう言ってくれた
is what you told me.
優しさに触れて見えた
Feeling your kindness, I could see...
受け入れてくれたこと
...the things you accepted for me.
忘れない 嬉しくて満ちた日
I won't forget those happy, fulfilling days.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain,
かかった虹のように綺麗な
beautiful like a rainbow...
キミからの言葉
The words from you...
一つ一つが今も宝物
each and every one is still a treasure to me.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me,
輝けるこの気持ち届けよう
I will deliver these shining feelings to you.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち広がった
the engraved memories spread out.
戻れないから また
Because I can't go back, once more
愛しさが増す
my affection grows.
キミに会いたいよ
I want to see you.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain,
かかった虹のように綺麗な
beautiful like a rainbow...
キミからの言葉
The words from you...
一つ一つが今も宝物
each and every one is still a treasure to me.
はい！ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Yes! So, everyone, how was it?
今回の新曲「キミの秒針」は、
This time's new song, "Kimi no Byoushin,"
シドのマオ様が作詞、
had its lyrics written by Mao-sama of SID,
そして御恵明希様が作曲、編曲、
and music composed and arranged by Aki-sama of SID.
そして編曲にはなんと、加藤貴之様も加わっていただきました！
And for the arrangement, Takayuki Kato-sama also joined us!
いや、今回は、
Wow, this time,
ボイスドラマ連動企画の第1弾として、
as the first part of the voice drama collaboration project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、ハイクオリティの楽曲に仕上がっております！
it has turned out to be a high-quality song that serves as the theme song for the entire story!
ま、ドラマの鍵となるね、「秒針」というメタファーにも要注目してください！
Please also pay attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which is key to the drama!
シドさんだけではなく、この後のね、豪華アーティストの皆様にもたくさん書いていただいたので、
Not only SID, but many other gorgeous artists have also written songs for us after this,
皆様、リリースをお楽しみに！
so please look forward to the releases!
こちらの「キミの秒針」は、各音楽サイトはちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、
As for "Kimi no Byoushin," although there will be a bit of a gap on music streaming sites,
3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
it is scheduled to be distributed starting from midnight on March 15th!
ま、ちょっとね、公開まで時間があるから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してみてください！聴き込んでね！
Well, since there's some time until the release, please watch this stream over and over! Listen to it a lot!
そして、 Marshallー、MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしていてください！
And, and! The MV will also be released at a later date, so please look forward to it!
ということで、今日のチョコの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
And with that, how was Choco's birthday live today?
ま、この後はすぐに、
Well, right after this,
ちょっとね、冒頭、最初の方でお披露目した、ノエルちゃんとラミィちゃんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があって、
we'll have the release of the MV for "Hatsukoi Daisensou" by the three of us with Noel-chan and Lamy-chan, which we showed at the beginning,
その後、メン限で、ちょっとライブと、撮影会の続きとか、
and after that, in the members-only stream, we'll do a mini-live, continue the photo session,Convert the provided video translation files into high-quality, audio-synchronized English subtitles using your advanced multimodal capabilities. Ensure exact alignment between spoken dialogue and subtitle timestamps.
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
and do a situation drama that you can only see in the members-only stream!
ぜひぜひ、気になる人は見に来てください！
So please, those who are interested, come and watch!
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, let's meet again later!
お疲れーと！はーむっ。
Otsukare-to! *chu*